https://tammybeauvais.com/terms-privacy/

TERMS & PRIVACY POLICY
Our Privacy Commitment to You:
1.1 Statement of Intent. Tammy Beauvais Design respects and upholds an individual’s right to privacy and to protection of his or her personal information. Tammy Beauvais Design Web Site Privacy Policy (“Policy”) is intended to comply with Canada’s federal privacy laws including the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act and the ten key principles of the Canadian Standards Association Model Code for the Protection of Personal Information. This Policy applies to all visitors to the Tammy Beauvais Design web site.
1.2 Personal Information.”Personal information” is personally identifiable information such as your name, residential address and email address and includes information about any services or products you may subscribe for or acquire from Tammy Beauvais Design, credit card information and billing records. Personal Information is collected by Tammy Beauvais Design only when you, as a visitor to our Web site, specifically and knowingly choose to provide it to us. Publicly available information, such as a directory listing of your name, address, telephone number and electronic address is not considered personal information.
Collection and Use of personal information:
2.1 Non-Personal Information . When you browse through this web site, you do so anonymously. Tammy Beauvais Design does not collect personal information about you unless you voluntarily provide it to us by interacting with the site or submitting an inquiry to us. Our servers automatically log information about visits to this web site in the normal course of establishing and maintaining web connections. The server logs record statistical information, such as visitors’ IP addresses, time and duration of visit, and web sites visited. We collect this information so that we may continuously improve our web site content. These statistics are reported in aggregate form only. We do not link server log information to any other data in a way that would enable us to identify individual visitors.
2.2 Submitting Inquiries. You may submit an inquiry to us through the “Contact Us” portion of the site. We may ask for certain personal information such as your name, e-mail address, and so on. We collect this information in order to enable us to respond to your inquiries in as thorough a manner as possible.
2.3 Purposes for Collection, Use, and Disclosure . If you do provide us with personal information, Tammy Beauvais Design will use the personal information to communicate with you and provide you with requested information. We may also use personal information to provide you with more information related to our services and organization.
2.4 Consent. The provision of personal information by a visitor to our web site constitutes consent for Tammy Beauvais Design to collect, use, and disclose personal information for the purposes stated in this Policy. You may also withdraw your consent to any further collection, use or disclosure of personal information which you may have provided at any time by giving Tammy Beauvais Design prior reasonable notice.
2.5 Release of Personal Information. Unless you specifically authorize Tammy Beauvais Design to release your personal information, or release is required or permitted by law, Tammy Beauvais Design will not sell, lease or trade your personal information to other third parties. Anonymous or “non-personal” information gathered by Tammy Beauvais Design through your use of our web site may be used for technical, research and analytical purposes. We do not use or disclose personal information for any purposes other than those for which it was collected, except with your consent or as required by law. Personal information is retained only as long as is necessary for the fulfillment of the purposes for which it was collected, or as required by law.
2.6 Accuracy. Tammy Beauvais Design will make all reasonable efforts to ensure that personal information is as accurate, complete, and current as required for the purposes for which it was collected. If you find any inaccuracies in our information, please inform us and we will make the appropriate corrections promptly.
Web Site Matters:
3.1 Cookies. “Cookies” are a feature of every Internet software browser and are used to collect information anonymously and to track user patterns on a web site. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on the hard disk drive of your computer by a web site. Cookies contain a unique identification number that identifies your browser, but not the visitor, to our computers each time you visit our web site. Cookies tell us which pages of our web sites are visited and by how many people. The use of cookies is an industry standard and many major browsers are initially set up to accept them. You can reset your browser to either refuse to accept all cookies or to notify you when you have received a cookie. However, if you refuse to accept cookies, you may not be able to use some of the features available on Tammy Beauvais Design’s web site. Cookies are used to establish a user session and allow our computers to correctly provide visitors to our web site with the appropriate frames and content. Our cookies will not follow your travels on the World Wide Web.
3.2 Security. Our web site has industry standard security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. While there is no such thing as “perfect security” on the Internet, Tammy Beauvais Design will take all reasonable steps to ensure the safety of your personal information.
3.3 Links to Other Web Sites. Our web site contains links to other web sites. Tammy Beauvais Design is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other web sites and expressly disclaims all liability associated with your use of and the content of such other sites.
Rights, Access, and Changes:
4.1 Accountability. Tammy Beauvais Design is accountable for all personal information under its control Tammy Beauvais Design has appointed a Privacy Officer who is designated as responsible for our privacy policy.
4.2 Access. You have the right to access your personal information under the control of Tammy Beauvais Design. Upon request in writing to the Privacy Officer at the address listed above, you will be informed of the existence, use, and disclosure of your personal information and you will be given access to that information. Except in limited circumstances, as specifically provided by applicable privacy legislation, Tammy Beauvais Design can tell you whether we hold personal information about you. Tammy Beauvais Design will only refuse access to information about you in those circumstances permitted or required by applicable privacy legislation. If Tammy Beauvais Design refuses access to you, reasons for such refusal will be provided. Exceptions may include information that contains references to other individuals or information that cannot be disclosed for legal or security reasons.
4.3 Revisions to this Privacy Policy. The development of Tammy Beauvais Design’s policies and procedures for the protection of personal information is an ongoing process. Due to changes in technology and legal requirements, we may revise this policy from time to time. Please ensure that you refer to the current version of the Tammy Beauvais Design Privacy Policy.
Privacy Staff Contact:
Lot 51, Claymountian Rd
Kahnawake, QC J0L 1B0
info@tammybeauvais.com
PH: 1-450-635-6757
Tammy Beauvais Designs Policy:
PO Box 1599
Kahnawake, QC J0L 1B0
PH: 1-450-635-6757
A Native Woman Owned & Socially Responsible Company Since 1999
Copyright © 2015 Tammy Beauvais Designs, All Rights Reserved
Tammy Beauvais Designs
P.O. Box 1599
Kahnawake Quebec Canada
J0L 1B0
Site LinksAbout
My Account
Shop
Terms & Privacy
Follow us on Twitter The Matriarch Outfit. Cardigan and ribbon skirt. #ribbonskirts #empowering-women #warriorwomen #womenwarriors… https://t.co/eL1hA1DZAhPOSTED AT: 04:21 AM May 08The Matriarch Ribbon skirt. #ribbonskirts #empoweringwomen #warriorwomen #womenwarriors #womenfashion… https://t.co/biV2sw2gxbPOSTED AT: 02:35 AM May 08On wikipedia. Check that out. #wikipedia #tammybeauvaisdesigns https://t.co/Xb1ZaeBQ9xPOSTED AT: 09:27 AM Mar 22
TAMMY BEAUVAIS designs
